<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="hello">Hello World, SpecialEffectsActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">SpecialEffects</string>
	<string name="choose_city">Please select the city</string>
	
	<string name="contact_title">iaiai - Contact</string>
	
	<string name="text1">IAIAI 测试</string>
	<string name="text2">测试跳转效果</string>
	<string name="next">下一页</string>
	
	<string name="detail_process_name">进程名称</string>
	<string name="kill_process">强制结束</string>
	<string name="detail_process_copyright">版权信息</string>
	<string name="detail_process_install_dir">安装目录</string>
	<string name="detail_process_data_dir">数据目录</string>
	<string name="detail_process_package_size">文件大小</string>
	<string name="detail_process_permission">操作权限</string>
	<string name="detail_process_service">服务信息</string>
	<string name="detail_process_activity">活动信息</string>
	
    <string name="silde">切换</string>
	<string name="sec">第2个Activity</string>
	<string name="setting">设置</string>
	<string name="text">This chapter introduced the Android platform and briefly touched on market positioning,
including what Android is up against in the rapidly changing mobile marketplace.
Inside two short years, the Android SDK has been announced, released, and
updated no fewer than four times. And that’s just the software. Major device manufacturers
have now signed on to the Android platform and have brought capable devices
to market, including a privately labeled device from Google itself. Android’s future
continues to brighten.
In this chapter, we examined the Android stack and discussed its relationship with
Linux and Java. With Linux at its core, Android is a formidable platform, especially
for the mobile space where it’s initially targeted. Although Android development is
done in the Java programming language, the runtime is executed in the Dalvik VM, as
an alternative to the Java VM from Oracle. Regardless of the VM, Java coding skills are
an important aspect of Android development.
We also examined the Android SDK’s Intent class. The Intent is what makes
Android tick. It’s responsible for how events flow and which code handles them. It
provides a mechanism for delivering specific functionality to the platform, enabling
third-party developers to deliver innovative solutions and products for Android. We
introduced all the main application classes of Activity, Service, ContentProvider,
and BroadcastReceiver, with a simple code snippet example for each. Each of these
application classes use Intents in a slightly different manner, but the core facility of
using Intents to control application behavior enables the innovative and flexible
Android environment. Intents and their relationship with these application classes
will be unpacked and unlocked as we progress through this book.
The AndroidManifest.xml descriptor file ties all the details together for an
Android application. It includes all the information necessary for the application to
run, what Intents it can handle, and what permissions the application requires.
Throughout this book, the AndroidManifest.xml file will be a familiar companion as
we add and explain new elements.
Finally, this chapter provided a taste of Android application development with a
simple example tying a simple UI, an Intent, and Google Maps into one seamless and
useful experience. This example is, of course, just scratching the surface of what
Android can do. The next chapter takes a deeper look into the Android SDK so that
you can learn more about the toolbox we’ll use to unlock Android.
		</string>
</resources>